Vrishab V Srivatsa

Data - Intern @ Juspay

Personal Website Sengaluru, India w vsrivatsa25@gmail.com +91 - 8296776590 Personal Website

vsrivatsa25

Profile

A 20 year old, currently located in Vellore, Tamil Nadu, India. Pursuing B. Tech in Computer Science and Engineering and specialising in Information Security from VIT Vellore (Batch of 2022). Interested in a career working in the information security domain.

Education

2018 - present **VIT University** Vellore, India

B. Tech, Computer Science and Engineering

Professional Experience

Dec 2020 - present

Technical Product Analyst (Data) - Intern

Bengaluru, India

Juspay

R & Shiny Programming | Data Analytics | Dashboard

Development

May 2020 - Sep 2020

Summer Intern

IIT Patna

Project - Signal Processing for Wireless

Communications Research Group, IIT-Patna.

Deliverable - Full Stack Development

Skills

Python Programming

Django

R / Shiny Programming

HTML

CSS

Javascript

MySQL

C / C++

Java

Cyber Security & Cryptographic Techniques

Git

Certificates

- Problem Solving through Programming in C Ø
- Python for Data Science ∂
- Network Security & Database Vulnerabilities Ø
- English for STEM by University of Pennsylvania
- Design and Analysis of Algorithms @
- Building Movies Site with Python & Django Ø

Projects

Image Encryption and Authentication @

Designed a custom image encryption and authentication algorithm based on Chaotic Mapping and perceptual hashing, implemented in the form of a Python GUI. Similar to the shuffling and reassembly of a Rubik's cube, yet randomized and unique to every secret key.

SocioHub 🔗

A Novel Social Networking Application to connect people from similar walks of life, with features like Content Filtering, Smart Suggestions and Connecting with Users. Runs on a Django Backend.

Covid Hospital Helper *⊘*

Assist hospitals in allocating beds for patients, prioritizing patients with underlying conditions, illnesses or anyone more vulnerable to the virus, using a random forest regressor model trained with COVID-19 patient data set from the Mexican Govt.

Publications

Apr 2019

Behavior Analysis of College Students in Academic and Non-Academic Zone - A Case Study

ISBN: 978-93-86782-78-6

Pages 91-96

• English • Hindi • Kannada Interests • Cricket • Photography • Graphic Design

Vrishab V Srivatsa vsrivatsa25@gmail.com 2 / 2